Harold Corsini Photographs, 1940s-1970s AIS.2007.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Job Number 2279- Steel Plant Exteriors (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2157- Pittsburgh Area Views (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2291- Westinghouse- Florida (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2293- Westinghouse- East Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2295- Hennepin Plant (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2300- Smithsonian Institution- Kellogg Media Group (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2303- Armco- Marsteller- Sample Images (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2304- Fecker- Mirror- Owens, Illinois, October 10, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2306- United States Steel- Alabama, October 28, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2311- Paul Wylie- Raleigh, North Carolina, November 15, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2313A- Bathroom Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2313B- Bathroom Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2313C- Bathroom Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2313D- Bathroom Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2316- Westinghouse- Kellogg Media Group (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2317- Fecker Optical- Toledo, Ohio (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2318- House Photographs (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2321- KM&G- Wearever Aluminum (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2327- Glassware (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2329- Aliquippa (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2331- Eljer Plumbing (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2333- Ross Street Building- Westinghouse Sales (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2334- KM&G- Westinghouse Circuit with Flame (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2336- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Columbus, Ohio (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2337- Papercraft (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2351- Marsteller- Rockwell Company- Nebraska, April 10, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2353- University of Pittsburgh- Oil Paintings, April 16, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2358- KM&G- Aerials (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2359- Paul Wylie- Armco- Marsteller- Take off Planes- Pittsburgh, Pa., May 6, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2360- Kansas, Missouri, and California (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2363- Bill Taylor- KM&G- Heinz, USA (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2364- Marsteller- Murrysville Valve (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2368- KM&G- Whistler's Mother- Pittsburgh Plate Glass (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2370- Equitable Life- Pittsburgh Aerial Views (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2373- KM&G- Pittsburgh Plate Glass- Tiaro Artist Studio (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2374- George. Luhmzin- J&L Steel Housing- Cleveland, Ohio, June 17, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2375- Hagen Computers (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2377- Basil Lee- Westinghouse Sky Train, July 9, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2378- KM&-G- Heinz (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2379- Dave Haynes- KM&G- Westinghouse- Charlotte, North Carolina, July 17, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2382- Basil Lee- Westinghouse- Sky Bus- Airport (Pittsburgh, Pa.) (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2287- Van Sant and Dugdale- Ludbaum Research Lab (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2390- Gatz- Portraits (Box 6, Folder 7, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2394A- George Prytula- Westinghouse- Model Sky Bus Station and Community (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2394B- Model Sky Bus Station and Community (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2397- Vandergrift- United States Steel (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2399- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Mill- Vandergrift, Pa. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2401A- Frank De Andre, Frank- Jay Reich- Saltsburg, Pa.- Papercraft (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2401B- Clothing Factory and Portraits (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2407- Cynthia Zeth- Marc Company- Crown Aluminum (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2412A- Flaherty Portraits (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2412B- Portraits (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2415- Polkington, North America- Rockwell- Mr. Wilson (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2419- Dave Barhouse- Sailboat (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2422- George Nama- Westmoreland Museum (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2427A- John Vranie- United States Steel, April 2, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2427B- United States Steel (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2428- FS&R Aircraft Engine (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2429- Bob Inch- FS&R; Coils of Wire (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2431- Nama- One Man Show- Westmoreland County (Pa.) Museum (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2432 - Bethlehem Steel- Vandergrift, Pa. (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2436A- Dave Haynes- Westinghouse- Lester Plant (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2436B- Dave Haynes- Westinghouse- Lester Plant (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2438- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Armco- Chairs (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2439- Milt Gutman- Glassware on Lawn (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2440- Westinghouse- Muddy Run Dam- George McKall (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2443- Mobley- Westinghouse- Heart Machine (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2445- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Armco- Chicago, June 23, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2446- George McKall- Westinghouse- Warren, Pa., June 23, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2447- Bob Inch- FS&R- Truck Wheel Hub (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2449- George Nama- Copies of Art Work (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2450- Paul Wylie- Zimmerman- Art- Marsteller- Fountain- New York (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2451- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich- Kmont, Oz (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2452- Howard Schweig- Griswold Eschelman- Girl with Bottle- Brockway Glass (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2455- Hugo DeZimmo- KM&G- Computer Parts- Westinghouse (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2456- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich House (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2457- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich Personal (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2459- Gene Daub- R. l. Stevenson- Shoes- 200 Chamber Commerce Building (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2460- McConnoughly- KM&G- Hand and Flame (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2461A- Howard Schweig- Griswold Eschelman- Girl with Picnic Table (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2461B- Glassware (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2464- Joe Cossetti- City Treasurer Portraits (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2466- Paul Wylie- DuBois, Pa. (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2467-Gerrard- Architecture- Duquesne University (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Job Number 2468- Bob Inch- FS&R- Plane Model and Clouds (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Job Number 2469- Bob Inch- FS&R- Aircraft Model and Clouds (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Job Number 2472- Walter Kollings -Compton, New York- United States Steel Cannon- Winchester, Virginia (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Job Number 2481- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich- Aluminum Plant- Butler, Pa. (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2482- Lue Glasso- Westinghouse Research Lab (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2483- Fred Fuller- Westinghouse- St. Louis, Mo. (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2484- Paul Wylie- Rockwell- North Carolina (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2486- Art Exhibit (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2494- Gene Daub- Stevenson- Safety Shoes (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2497- Ollie Jochumsen- Heibrich and Held Cyclops, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2498- Jack Elster- KM&G- Westinghouse Model (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2500- Milt Gutman- Glassware (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2502- Bob Inch- FS&R- Aircraft Model and Clouds (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2505- Gene Daub- R. L. Stevenson- Desert Shot of Shoes (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2507- Art Zimmerman- Marsteller- Rockwell Research (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2511- Art Zimmerman- Marsteller- Rockwell Test (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2512- Dick Lyle- Marsteller- Rockwell Valve Cutaway (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2513- Milt Gutman- Crystalware (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2514- Gene Daub- R. L. Stevenson- Heavy Work Shoes (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2518- Bill Taylor- KM&G- McIntosh- Heinz Plant (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2519- Bob Inch- FS&R- Man with Sunglasses (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2520- Bob Inch- FS&R- Road Machines- Indiana (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2521- Gene Daub- R. L. Stevenson- Iron Age Shoes (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2522-Tom McIntosh- Heinz- Country Club (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2523- Dick Lyle- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Rockwell- DuBois, Pa.- Meter Tree (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2525- John Uranic- Extra Prints (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2525A- John Uranic- United States Steel (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2525B- John Uranic- United States Steel (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2527- Ian Kochmanski- Marsteller's Rockwell- Meteo Sculptor (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2528- Bob Inch- FS&R- Pressure Vessels- Alcoa (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2530- Gene Daub- R. L. Stevenson- Iron Cage Shoes- Heavy Work Type (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2535- Washington, D.C.- Shopping Plaza (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2536- Gene Daub- R. L. Stevenson- Iron Age Dress (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2537- Bill Shaver- Precise Metals and Plaster Company (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2537A- Bill Shaver- Contact Prints (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2538- Suchy [?], Bill- FS&R- Highway Signs (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2539- Joe McKenna- Marstetler's Rockwell Valve Cutaway (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2540- Joe Mack- KM&G- Westinghouse Modular Panel Hood (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2541- Ted Mack- Light Bulbs (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2542- Erikson McCann- Mellon Bank Kids (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2543- Sam Hazo- Candids (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2544- Precise Metals Portraits (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2545- Dick Lyle- Marsteller- Rockwell Meter (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2546- Hal Boyles-Elger, November 10, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2547- Portrait (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Job Number 2547A- Oliver- Christmas Card, November 2, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Job Number 2548- John Uranic- United States Steel- Steel Slivers (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Job Number 2550- Gruenbaum- Portraits of Girl (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Job Number 2551- Bob Inch- FS&R- Electronics- Alcoa (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Job Number 2552- Al Kiefer- FS&R- Alcoa- Florida, December 8, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Job Number 2554- Bob Inch- FS&R- Alcoa, December 17, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Job Number 2555- John Wyant- KM&G- Westinghouse- East Pittsburgh, Pa., December 16, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Job Number 2556- John Uranic- United States Steel- Candids (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2557- Ollie Jackumsen- Heibich and Held- Metal Sheets Cyclops (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Job Number 2558- Ewing Brown- United States Steel (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Job Number 2559- Bernie Vangrin- KM&G- Richmond, Virginia- Telephone Company (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2560- George Titonis- KM&G- Boston (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2561- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich- Umbrella (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2563- Hal Boyles- Elger- Shower and Stall Units (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2564- Ted Mack- KM&G- Computer (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2565- Ralph Lees- Precise Prototype (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2566- Pershing Alum Sculpture (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2567- Bob Ross- Rumrill Hay- Rochester Filter (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2568- Al Kiefer- FS&R- Little Boy- London Bridge (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2569A- Hal Boyles- Elger Plumbing Fixtures (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2569B- Elger Plumbing (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2570- Frank De Andre- Radio- Listerine (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2571- Kelly- Macrame- Painting (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2572- Neighbor Portrait (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2573- Bob Inch- Alum Parts- Girl (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2574- Dick Lyle- Ed Corbett- Marsteller- Model Wabco Transit (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2576- Bob Ross- Filter (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2577- Gutman- Glassware (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2578- Bernie Vangrin- KM&G- Stauffer's Food Varieties (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2579- Bob Inch- FS&R- Alcoa Metal (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2580- Ed Corbett- Marsteller- Plumber Tools (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2581- Ted Mack- KM&G- Westinghouse- 'Up' (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2582-Airport Hangar (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2583- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Hangar Building and Valve (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2584- Hal Boyles- Elger Plumbing- Bathrooms (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2585- George Titonis- KM&G- Doorway (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2586- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Subway (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2587- Gary Merola- Plastic Book Ends (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2587- Gary Merola- Plastic Book Ends (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2588- Meltzer (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2589- Newman (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2590- Rosenbloom- Christmas Cards (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2591-Ted Mack- KM&G- Transformers (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2592-Jack Wadsworth- R. L. Stevenson- Shoes (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2593- Frank De Andre- Lincoln Homes- Franklin, Pa. (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2594- Gutman (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2595- John Lunz- Papercraft (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2596- William Mueller- Life Assurance (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2597- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich- Lincoln Homes- Franklin, Pa. (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2598- Dick Lyle- Marstelle- Wabco- Canada (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2599- Julius Younger Portraits (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2600- Jack Wadsworth- R. L. Stevenson- Shoes (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2603- Al Kiefer- Oakmont Golf Club- Alcoa, October 1972 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Job Number 2604- Paul Wylie- Valve Wabco, October 1972 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Job Number 2605- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Rockwell- Setup at Weinhold (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Job Number 2606- Frank De Andre- Jay Reich- Lincoln Homes (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Job Number 2607- Allen Anderson- Portraits (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Job Number 2609- Eljer- Boyles- Funny Pores- November 1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Job Number 2610 -Ralph Marmo- Papercraft Post Cards (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Job Number 2611- Al Sclipiner [?] (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Job Number 2612- Bob Inch- Alcoa Window with Models (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Job Number 2613- Jack Elster- Kellogg Media Group- East Pittsburgh- Westinghouse- Motors (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Job Number 2615- Al Kiefer- Alcoa Window- Nude- House (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Job Number 2616-Jack Elster- Westinghouse Atomic Bomb (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Job Number 2617- Rosenbloom Concert (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Job Number 2618- Gutman- Cut Glass (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Job Number 2619- Pierce Platt- Santa (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Job Number 2620- Industrial (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Job Number 2621- Wylie- Motors, etc. (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Job Number 2622- Katy- Portraits, January 1973 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Job Number 2623- Paul Wylie- Rockwell Meters, January 1973 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Job Number 2624- Al Kiefer- Alcoa- Siding and Man (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Job Number 2625- Negatives Loaned by Library (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Job Number 2627- President of Jones and Laughlin Steel Company (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Job Number 2628- Paul Wylie- Rockwell, February 1973 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Job Number 2629- Hal Boyles- Elger- School Toilets (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2630- Paul Wylie- Lima, Ohio (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2631- Jack Woodsworth- R. L. Stevenson- Shoes, March 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2632- Hugo DeZimo (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2633A- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Wabco- Jasper, April 1973 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2633B- Train and Tracks in Mountains (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2633C- Wabco- Computers- Wiring (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2634- Lewis- Oxford Dewlight- South Hills Shopping, April 1973 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2635- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Clocks- Meter Man, April 1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2636- McKall- Westinghouse- Elmira (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2637- DeAndre, Frank- Family- Blue Cross (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2638- Shopping Center, April 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2639- Levin- Old Age Home- Architect's Model (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2640- Paul Morgan- Oberg Manufacturing Company, Inc., May 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2641- Advertising (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2642- Feldman- Pittsburgh Plate Glass- Fiberglass Chopper, June 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2644- Marmo (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2645- Dick, June 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2646- Paul Wylie- Marsteller- Wheeling Steel Building, July 1973 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2647- R. L. Stevenson- Shoes (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2649- Al Pasti- Alcoa Labs (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2648- Wylie- Pipe Cleaner- Marsteller- Rockwell (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2650- Al Pasti- Alcoa- Car, August 1973 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2651- Al Kiefer- FS&R- Alcoa- Cedar Logs (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2700- Copperweld- Warren, Ohio, September 1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2701- Precise Metals and Plastics (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2702- Deb Shapino (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2705- Ed Korbett- Parking Meter- Water Meter- Rockwell (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2706- Seltzer (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2710- Ed Korbett- Blair Products (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2708- Jack Wadsworth- Iron Age Shoes (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2711A- Ed Korbett- Gas Meter (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2711B- Hal Boyles- Elger (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2715- Lubetz- Architectural Models, February 1974 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2717- Architect Gerard (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2718- DeAndre- Doc Muffy (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2719- East Palestine, September 1974 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2720- Copperweld, October 1974 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2721- Wadsworth- Stevenson- Shoes- Outdoors (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2722- Burt Delano- Cyclops Manifold (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2724- Arco Medical (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Job Number 2726-Wabco- Atlanta, January 1976 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Job Number 2800- Gerard (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Job Number 2801- DeAndre- Furniture (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Job Number 2802- Harold Personal- Damianos (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Job Number 2803- Medical (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Job Number 2806- Carnegie Mellon University Negatives (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Job Number 2809- Industrial (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Job Number 2810- Eyes (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Job Number 2811- Advertising (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Job Number 2812- Portraits (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Job Number 2813- Fallingwater (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Job Number 2815- Topical (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Job Number 2816- Fallingwater (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Job Number 2818- Nature and Architecture (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Job Number 2819- New York City (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Job Number 2820- Travel (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Job Number 2821- Travel (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Job Number 2822B- Travel (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Job Number 2822C- Topical Travel (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Job Number 2823- Field and Harold Portrait (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Job Number 2900- Pierce- Portraits (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Job Number 2901- Statues (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Job Number 2902- Harold Portraits (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Job Number 2903- Advertising (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Job Number 2903A- Westinghouse- United States Steel- Alcoa- Armco- Advertising, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Job Number 2904-Topical Travel, ca. 1941-1949/ca. 1950-1955 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Job Number 2915- Oakland (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Job Number [N/A]- Unidentified Man Welding (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Job Number [N/A]- Personal (Box 10, Folder 71)